Mss.B.J44 Mss.B.J44
American Philosophical Society
- Papers
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Dec. 3, 1930; 11x8-1/2; Hazlitt, Henry, 1894-1993
    New York, Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Asks him to review a book.
  - Letter to [Herbert S.] Jennings, Dec. 12, 1930; 8-1/2x5-1/2; Hazlitt, Henry, 1894-1993
    New York, Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning a book review.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Dec. 11, 1930; 10x8; Hedley, J W
    A.L.S. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Asks question.
  - Account with H.S. Jennings, April 25, June 30, 1920-1945; Henry Holt and Company
    D. 23 items. Various sizes. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Royalty statements for the anatomy of the cat.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, March 28, 1921; 8-1/2x5-1/2; Henry Holt and Company
    New York, Typed L.s.: A[rthur] W. Burnett. 1p., end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Business.
  - Letter to [Herbert S.] Jennings, Sept. 25, 1933; 11x8-1/2; Herrick, C. Judson (Charles Judson), 1868-1960
    Chicago, A.L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Friendly letter.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Los Angeles, June 14, 1940; 11x8-1/2; Herzfeld, Karl F. (Karl Ferdinand), 1892-
  - Letter to H[erbert] S[pencer] Jennings, April 18, 1931; 6-3/4x5-1/2; Hinkel, F Whitehill
    Buffalo, A.L.S. 2p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Friendly letter.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Oct. 1, 1933; 7x6; Hinkel, F Whitehill
    Buffalo, A.L.S. 3p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Friendly letter.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Los Angeles, Jan. 7, 1941; 3-1/4x5-1/2; Hofer, Alvin William, 1903-
    Geneva, N.Y., A.L.S. on postal card. 1p.,end.and add. (see H.S. Jennings papers) Asks for reprint.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Dec. 18, 1923; 10-1/2x7-1/2; Hollander, Jacob Harry, 1871-1940
    Baltimore, Typed L.S. 1p., end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Friendly letter.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, March 17, 1924; 10-1/2x7-1/2; Hollander, Jacob Harry, 1871-1940
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Oct. 10, 1924; 10-1/2x7-1/2; Hollander, Jacob Harry, 1871-1940
    Baltimore, Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Thanks for reprints of an article.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Jan. 29, 1924; 11x8-1/2; Holmes, Samuel J. (Samuel Jackson), 1868-1964
    Berkeley, Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Friendly letter. Thanks for publications. Refers to immigration.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Jan. 15, 1940; 11x8-1/2; Holmes, Samuel J. (Samuel Jackson), 1868-1964
    Berkeley, Typed L.S. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Business.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Los Angeles, Oct. 7, 1941; 11x8-1/2; Hull, Edwin D
    Gary, Ind., Typed L.S. 2p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning eugenics.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Sept. 9, 1930; 11x8-1/2; Hunt, Harrison Randall, 1889-
    East Lansing, Mich., Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings Papers.) Congratulates him on his book.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Jan. 2, 1941; 5-1/2x8-1/2; Hunter, George W. (George William), 1902-
    Claremont, Cal., Typed L.S. 1p., end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Wishes to use prints from his publication.
  - Letter to [Herbert S.] Jennings, Jan. 27, 1941; 5-1/2x8-1/2; Hunter, George W. (George William), 1902-
    Claremont, Cal., Typed L.S. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Thanks for permission to use print from his publication.
  - Letter to Herbert Spencer Jennings, Baltimore, Feb. 9, 1934; 11x8-1/2; Independent Woman
    New York, Typed L.S.: Winifred Willson. 2p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Asks that he Contribute an article.
  - Letter to Herbert Spencer Jennings, Baltimore, Feb. 21, 1934; 10-3/4x8-1/2; Independent Woman
    New York, Typed L.S.: Winifred Willson. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers) Business.
  - Letter to Herbert Spencer Jennings, Baltimore, March 14, 1934; 10-3/4x8-1/2; Independent Woman
    New York, Typed L.S.: Winifred Willson. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers) Concerning a possible article.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, May 7, 1934; 11x8-1/2; Independent Woman
    New York, Typed L.S.: Winifred Willson. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Returns article.
  - Letter to [Herbert S. Jennings], [1930]; 8-1/2x7; Internation press-cutting bureau
    London, L. 4p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Wishes to provide him with clippings for a fee.
  - Letter to [Herbert S. Jennings, 1930; International press-cutting bureau
    L. 1p.and 3p.of enc. Various sizes. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Would be glad to send him clippings for a fee.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, May 6, 1938; 11x8-1/2; Jacobs, M. H. (Merkel Henry), 1884-1974
    Philadelphia, Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Asks that he form a special group for the forthcoming meeting of the American society of zoologists.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, May 13, 1938; 11x8-1/2; Jacobs, M. H. (Merkel Henry), 1884-1974
    Philadelphia, Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning speeches for the meeting.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Aug. 12, 1930; 10x8, 11x8-1/2; Jenkins, A H
    New York, Typed L.S. 1p.and enc.of 1p. and (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Asks question on eugenics.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Oct. 7, 1930; 10x8; Jenkins, A H
    New York, Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Thanks for his letter on eugenics.
  - Outline for a symposium, Dec., 1938; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    A.D. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.)
  - Papers, 1893-1947; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    D. 893 items and 47 printed items. Various sizes. 2boxes corres.and 485 picture postals cards,etc. For table of contents, see first black box. Donated by Mrs. Vernon Lynch, 1947 and 1957. Table of contents available.
  - Papers., Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    D. ca.200 letters pertaining chiefly to the 7th International Zoological Congress at Boston, 1907. Includes photographs and postals. Various sizes. Presented by Mrs. Vernon Lynch, 1967.
  - Problems in the study of genetics in lower organisms, 1917; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Mimeographed D. 13p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.)
  - Proposed outline for a symposium, Dec. 22, 1938; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    A.D. 1p. In pencil. (see H.S. Jennings.)
  - Self-consciousness in animals, Feb. 4, 1936; 8-1/2x5-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    A.D. 20 leaves. (see H.S. Jennings papers.)
  - Telegram to Geddes Smith, New York, Nov. 27, [1923]; 8-1/2x5-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    A.D.S. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Business.
  - Telegram to Geddes Smith, New York, Dec. 3, 1923; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
  - Telegram to The Survey, New York, Dec., [1923]; 5-1/2x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
  - Ageing., 1941; 8-1/2x5-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Sigma Xi address at Chicago; A.D. 35p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.)
  - Biological aspects of charity, 1930; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed D. 18p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Printed: in Intelligent philanthropy, 1930.
  - Biology of democracy, 1926; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    A.D. 7 leaves. In pencil and ink. Various sizes. (see H.S. Jennings papers
  - Book review of Crime and Destiny, 1930; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    A.D. 8 leaves. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) ----Typed copy. 2p. Printed: The Nation; Jan. 14, 1931.
  - Book review of von Eulenburg-Wiener's book: Fearfully and Wonderfully Made..., May 10, 1938; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed D. 3p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.)
  - Indiana lecture notes (supplementary pages, not needed), 1943; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    A.D. 6p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.)
  - Indiana lectures (miscellaneous notes), 1946-1947; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    A.D. and typed D. 17 leaves. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning genetics.
  - Lecture on age and death in protozoa, May 10, 1943; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    A.D. 26p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Delivered at the university of California.
  - Letter to Jerome Alexander,New York, Jan. 13, 1942; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p.,end. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning a publication.
  - Letter to Jerome Alexander, New York, July 27, 1942; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Friendly letter.
  - Letter to the American naturalist, Lancaster, Nov. 29, 1939; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Asks concerning reprints of an article.
  - Letter to Moses J. Aronson, New York, June 25, 1941; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p.,end. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning articles to be published.
  - Letter to Richard G. Badger, Boston, Dec. 6, 1920; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p.,end. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Business.
  - Letter to Elsie Barnes, Culver City, Cal., Oct. 2, 1930; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
  - Letter to Ruth Bunier [Bernier], New Haven, May 29, 1933; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. Copy (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning galley proofs of his publication.
  - Letter to Jacob Billikopf, Philadelphia, Sept. 30, 1930; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Thanks for his compliments.
  - Letter to Herbert Blumer, Chicago, Oct. 18, 1941; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning the publication of his article.
  - Letter to P. P. Boyd, Lexington, Ky., March 20, 1918; 8-1/2x5-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 2p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Recommends Cowles for position.
  - Letter to P.P. Boyd, Lexington, Ky., April 12, 1918; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    A.L. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Recommends Cowles for position.
  - Letter to Paul Brockett, Washington, Sept. 28, 1942; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p.,end. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings.papers.) Concerning a biographical memoir of Raymond Pearl.
  - Letter to H. E. Buchholz, Baltimore, March 26, 1924; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning sociologiacl studies.
  - Letter to Luther Burbank, Santa Rosa, Calif., Oct. 7, 1924; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
  - Letter to Philip Burnet, Wilmington, June 19, 1921; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    A.L.S.with initials. 10p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) ----Copy. Typed. Concerning environment vs. heredity.
  - Letter to Philip Burnet, Wilmington, June 23, 1921; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Ocean City, Md., A.L.S. 6p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) ----Typed copy. Concerning problems of intelligence.
  - Letter to E. G. Butler, Princeton, July 5, 1938; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning proposed program on genetics
  - Letter to E. G. Butler, Princeton, Oct. 1, 1938; 6x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. Incomplete. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning titles of papers to be read.
  - Letter to E. G. Butler, Princeton, Oct. 8, 1938; 8-1/2x5-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Business.
  - Letter to E. G. Butler, Princeton, Oct. 20, 1938; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning equipment necessary for papers to be read at a meeting.
  - Letter to E. G. Butler, Princeton, Oct. 31, 1938; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning the papers they are to read.
  - Letter to E. G. Butler, Princeton, Nov. 2, 1938; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning papers to be read.
  - Letter to Garry [sic] N. Calkins, New York, Oct. 12, 1920; 8-1/2x5-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
  - Letter to [Gary N.] Calkins, New York, Nov. 1, 1937; 8-1/2x5-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
  - Letter to G[ary] N. Calkins, New York, Oct. 11, 1939; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning his publication.
  - Letter to Philip P. Calvert, Philadelphia, July 17, 1939; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
  - Letter to Jacques [sic] Cattell, Lancaster, Dec. 1, 1938; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning a publication of articles.
  - Letter to Jacques [sic] Cattell, Lancaster, Jan. 14, 1939; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning the publication of some articles.
  - Letter to J. McKeen Cattell, Garrison, N.Y., Oct. 17, 1941; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Forwards manuscript for publication.
  - Letter to W. L. Chamberlain, Meriden, Jan. 25, 1924; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Conn.; Typed L. 1p.,end. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning the study of evolution and Mendelism.
  - Letter to T. A. Clower, Douglas, Ga., Oct. 20, 1932; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
  - Letter to the Columbia university press, New York, June 2, 1924; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
  - Letter to E[dwin] G. Conklin, Philadelphia, June 5, 1941; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Sends abstract.
  - Letter to Joseph Corrigan, Washington, March 6, 1939; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p.,end. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Will try to finish his article for publication.
  - Letter to E. V. Cowdry, St. Louis, Dec. 5, 1938; 8-1/2x5-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Will attend committee meeting.
  - Letter to E. V. Cowdry, St. Louis, Feb. 13, 1939; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 3p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning aging.
  - Letter to E. V. Cowdry, St. Louis, Aug. 8, 1941; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    A.L.S. 1p.and enc.of 5p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) ----Typed copy. Pertaining to an article in a publication.
  - Letter to R. P. Cowles, Manila, June 30, 1919; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 2p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Friendly letter.
  - Letter to R. P. Cowles, Manila, July 1, 1919; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning a position which is open.
  - Letter to Mrs. R. P. Cowles, New York, June 30, 1919; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
  - Letter to Malcolm Cowley, New York, April 16, 1931; 8-1/2x5-1/2, 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p.and enc.of 3p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Encloses book review (which was published April? May? 1931 of the New Republic.)
  - Letter to Wilbur L. Cross, New Haven, Feb. 1, 1933; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning a publication.
  - Letter to Bartley C. Crum, Hollywood, Calif., Aug. 20, 1946; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Would like to accept sponsorship of The Nation Associates dinner.
  - Letter to Eugene A. Davidson, New Haven, May 9, 1933; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning the title of his new publication.
  - Letter to Eugene A. Davidson, June 15, 1933; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    New Haven Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning punctuation in his new publication.
  - Letter to Bradley M. Davis, Ann Arbon, Oct. 3, 1921; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
  - Letter to Dorothy Davis, New York, Dec. 20, 1938; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Asks to change his article for publication.
  - Letter to Dorothy Davis, New York, Jan. 6, 1939; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p.,end. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Sends prints for publication with his papers.
  - Letter to L. V. Domm, Chicago, Nov. 27, 1940; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p.and enc.of 3p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Sends biographical memoir of Dr. Pearl.
  - Letter to Norman V. Donaldson, New Haven, Sept. 15, 1933; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 2p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning copies of his book.
  - Letter to Mrs. W.F. [Ethel S.] Dummer, Chicago, Feb. 28, 1931; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning their publication on progressive education. Friendly letter.
  - Letter to G. D. Eaton, New York, April 28, 1927; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
  - Letter to G. D. Eaton, New York, Aug. 20, 1927; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning an article for Plain talk.
  - Letter to G. D. Eaton, New York, Oct. 31, 1927; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning the possibility of an article on genetics.
  - Letter to G. D. Eaton, New York, Dec. 21, 1927; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning an article for publication.
  - Letter to G. D. Eaton, New York, Dec. 28, 1927; 9-1/4x7-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning an article submitted for publication.
  - Letter to G. D. Eaton, New York, Jan. 2, 1928; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
  - Letter to G. D. Eaton, New York, Jan. 6, 1928; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Asks for reprints of an article.
  - Letter to G. D. Eaton, New York, Jan. 9, 1928; 9-3/4x7-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
  - Letter to E. M. East, Boston, Nov. 29, 1933; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning an article on genetics.
  - Letter to Eleanor Erickson, St. Peter, Minn., March 10, 1924; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p.,end. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning immigration.
  - Letter to Henry F. Fletcher, Hazardville, Conn., Jan. 3, 1934; 8-1/2x5-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
  - Letter to [William J. Fox], Feb. 19, 1924; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning a publication on Leidy.
  - Letter to W[illia]m J. Fox, Philadelphia, Feb. 27, 1924; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p.,end. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning a publication on Leidy.
  - Letter to Thomas S. Gates, Philadelphia, July 17, 1939; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Will participate in the bicentennial celebration of the U of P.
  - Letter to G. F. Gause, Moscow, Jan. 11, 1941; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning an article. For article. see: G.F. Gause. The effect of natural selection...; 1940.
  - Letter to Frances Gehr, Pittsburgh, March 5, 1925; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Forwards publications.
  - Letter to Genetics, New York, Nov. 11, 1938; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Forwards an article for possible publication.
  - Letter to Genetics, New York, Dec. 14, 1938; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning an article to be published.
  - Letter to Genetics, New York, Jan. 2, 1939; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning an article.
  - Letter to Arthur C. Giese, Sept. 20, 1938; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning a paper which he is to read.
  - Letter to Arthur C. Giese, Oct. 8, 1938; 8-1/2x5-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning an article to be read.
  - Letter to A[rthur] C. Geise [sic], Jan. 14, 1939; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. Copy (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Can publish their papers in he wishes.
  - Letter to John M. Gillman, Pittsburgh, Feb. 20, 1924; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
  - Letter to William M. Goldsmith, Winfield, Kans., May 6, 1925; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Forwards publication, with news of same.
  - Letter to E. S. Goodrich, Oxford, Eng., Feb. 12, 1924; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p.,end. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Grants permission for reproduction from a publication.
  - Letter to B. Howell Griswold, jr., Baltimore, Nov. 9, 1933; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
  - Letter to Ross G. Harrison, New Haven, Jan. 11, 1941; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Encloses paper by G.F. Gause for publication.
  - Letter to R[oss] G. Harrison, New Haven, April 26, 1944; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Forwards paper for publication.
  - Letter to Ross G. Harrison, New Haven, Oct. 5, 1944; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
  - Letter to Henry Hazlitt, New York, Dec. 11, 1930; 8-1/2x5-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning a book review.
  - Letter to Henry Hazlitt, New York, Dec. 26, 1930; 8-1/2x5-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Encloses book review.
  - Letter to S. J. Holmes, Berkeley, Feb. 5, 1924; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
  - Letter to Harrison [R.] Hunt, East Lansing, Mich., Sept. 29, 1930; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947